I feel things have been going well up to this point & I am happy to help out, but I think there is still confusion about my skill set.  I told Tim I would help Syed get set up in the AMEX environment, but I have never done a SharePoint migration.  I am happy to help with the migration but do not at this point have the skills to lead it.  Can you tell me who the lead tech is on it, so I can refer Syed to the correct person when needed?